我们家猎魔  我们就做这个
My family hunts, it's what we do.
我们开始吧
Let's begin.
(走过的路)
图妮·贝维尔  记录者  伦敦分会的
Toni Bevell, Men of Letters, London chapter house.
但如果你回答我的问题  你就能走出去了
If you answer my questions, you'll walk right out that door.
我被魔鬼本人折磨过
I've been tortured by the Devil himself.
你能把我怎么样
What can you do to me?
温家兄弟不比他们控制不了的
The Winchesterst are no better than the monsters
那些怪物强到哪去
they fail to control.
他们该被铲除
They need to be eliminated.
我们不是一队的吗
Aren't we supposed to be on the same team?
别碰我儿子
Get away from my boys.
妈妈
Mom?
‭没错
Yeah.
毫无疑问  贝维尔夫人太过分了
No argument. Lady Bevell went too far.
我深表歉意
I deeply apologize.
我们想跟你们合作  我的号码
We wanna work with you. My number.
我发现了个案子
I found a case.
如果妈妈想猎魔  我们就去
And if Mom wants to hunt, I say we hunt.
我听说过人死而复生
I've heard of people coming back from the dead before.
但自己活过来
But to actually do it?
我有好多空白要填补
I just have a lot of blanks to fill in.
我得走了
I have to go.
看到温家人不能如愿
It's always nice to see a Winchester
总是很爽的
who can't get what he wants.
比莉  她是个死神
Billie. She's a reaper.
我坚信死了的
See, I'm a big believer in what dies...
萨姆
Sam!
-不该活过来  -不
- ...stays dead. ‭- No!
不  迪恩
Stop it! Dean.
如果你们任何一个改主意了
If any of you change your minds,
你们知道我叫什么
you know my name.
我们得把路西法关回笼子里
We've got to put Lucifer back in the cage.
我认为  我知道路西法最新皮囊是谁了
I think I know the identity of Lucifer's newest vessel --
杰夫森·鲁尼
Jefferson Rooney,
美国总统
President of these United States.
我知道你肯定会成为个好父亲
I just know you'd make an amazing father.
一个拿非利人要诞生了
A nephilim is come into being.
就是天使和凡人的后代
It's the offspring of an angel and a human.
路西法
Lucifer.
你要用那个把路西法从总统身体里赶出去
So you're gonna pop Lucifer out of the President with that?
希望能行  否则我们死定了
I hope so. Otherwise, we're all dead.
你们因企图行刺美国总统
You're under arrest for the attempted assassination
被捕了
of the President of the United States.
我们又不是
It's not like we're in the
做"活到九十  美梦长眠"那行的
"Live till you're 90, die in your sleep" Business.
只有一个结局
This only ends one way.
(如今)
卡西迪奥
Castiel?
玛丽  你在哪
Mary. Where are you?
我...
I-I, uh...
堪萨斯州  劳伦斯
Lawrence, Kansas.
小卡  怎么了
Cass, what's wrong?
我需要你去地堡见我
Well, I-I need you to meet me at the bunker.
六小时前  萨姆和迪恩·温彻斯特
Six hours ago, Sam and Dean Winchester
企图刺杀美国总统
tried to kill the President of the United States.
知道为什么吗
Do we know why?
我们逮捕他们后  他们还一言未发
They haven't said a word since we picked 'em up.
不说话  好吧  我们对他们有什么了解
Quiet types, okay. What do we know about 'em?
了解不少  他们是兄弟
A lot. Brothers.
生于堪萨斯州  劳伦斯
Born in Lawrence, Kansas,
母亲玛丽·温彻斯特  已死亡
to Mary Winchester, deceased,
父亲约翰·温彻斯特  也已死亡
and John Winchester, also deceased.
联调局于2007年就开始调查他们
FBI started investigating them back in 2007.
-为什么  -袭击  杀人
- For what? - Assault, murder,
多次损毁尸体
multiple counts of desecrating a corpse.
同一具尸体吗
The same corpse?
不  多具尸体
No. Different corpses.
他们2011年登上联调局头号通缉犯榜
They made the FBI's Most Wanted in 2011,
然后在爱荷华州安克尼市与警方枪战时死去
then died in a shootout with police in Ankeny, Iowa.
至少档案上是这么写的  但显然并非如此
At least that's what their file said, but apparently not.
显然是的  那女孩呢
Apparently. What about the girl?
凯莉·克莱恩  她是总统助理
Kelly Kline. And she's a Presidential aide,
但那天之后再没人见过她
but no one's seen her since that day.
我们不清楚她去了哪  或是是否还活着
We don't know where she went or if she's still alive.
多少人知道此事
How many people know about this?
我们在低调处理
We're keeping it quiet.
只有你  我  进行逮捕的特工和总统
Just you, me, the agents who made the arrest, and POTUS.
但他只记得
But the last thing he remembers...
事发前三天晚上做祈祷
was saying his nightly prayers three days before it happened.
-被下药了吗  -实验室正在进行毒检
- Drugged? - Lab's running a tox screen now,
但是可能吧
but yeah, probably.
"可能"就是"不确定"
And by "probably," you mean "maybe."
"不确定"就是"我不知道"
And by "maybe," you mean "I don't know."
下次  直说不知道就好
So next time, just say you don't know.
听着
Look,
找你来  是因为你是反恐专家
you're here because you're some big shot anti-terrorism guy.
但要我说
But you want my opinion?
我们应该把那俩疯子带去后面
We should take those two psychos out back.
我干掉一个  你负责另一个  早点去吃午饭
I cap one, you take the other, we grab an early lunch.
-是吗  -他们活该
- Yeah? - They got it comin'.
嗯  但如果他们不是单独作案呢
Yeah, but what if they're not working alone?
如果他们还跟...比如
I mean, what if these boys have ties to...Oh, I don't know,
白人民族主义者或穆斯林兄弟会有联系呢
white nationalists, Muslim brotherhood?
不是吧
Really?
我就是说说
I'm just sayin'.
他们或许是什么可怕的冰山的一角呢
They might be the tip of some nasty-ass iceberg.
-你是这么想的吗  -可能吧
- That -- that's what you think? - Probably.
不确定
Maybe.
我不知道
I don't know.
去问问看
Let's find out.
迪恩
Dean.
你好吗
How you doin'?
要咖啡吗  或是水
Can I get you coffee? Water?
你饿了吗
Or you hungry?
我身上有巧克力棒
I got a chocolate bar here somewhere.
别告诉我妻子
Don't tell my wife.
你今天挺够呛啊
So...you've had a day.
想跟我说说吗
Wanna tell me about it?
比如
Like, for example,
你为什么要刺杀自由世界的领袖
why you went after the leader of the free world?
我猜猜  你不喜欢警察
Well, let me guess. You don't like cops.
我理解
Hell, I get it.
我们有时很混蛋
We can be real jackasses.
但你会对我开口的  孩子
But you're gonna talk to me, son.
你会的
You just are.
这不是威胁
Now that's not a threat.
我不相信酷刑  那不好使
I don't believe in torture. Doesn't work.
我见过人受水刑  被割伤
I've seen folks waterboarded, cut on.
他们的确会侃侃而谈
And they talk. Ooh, they do.
但他们绝不会说出你想听的
But they never tell you what you need.
你知道什么好使吗  屡试不爽
You know what does work, though? Every time?
虚无
Nothing.
我走后
See, when I leave,
那扇门就会关闭
that door closes,
不会再打开
and it stays closed,
你会被关在黑暗里
and you stay in the dark.
听上去可能也没那么糟
Now maybe that doesn't sound so bad.
但一个月后  一年后
But after a month, a year,
你盯这几面墙盯得足够久
you spend enough time staring at these walls,
只有你  和那一片虚无
just you and all that nothing,
你会很想开口  好见到个真人
you'll get so crazy to talk, to see someone real,
你会告诉我我想听的
you'll tell me exactly what I need.
你会笑着告诉我
You'll tell me with a smile.
只是需要点时间
It'll just take some time.
当然了  问题是
Of course, the thing is,
你做了那样的事
after what you did,
不会有人急着让你打电话
no one's in a hurry to get you that phone call.
你和我
So you and me,
我们有的是时间
we've got all the time in the world.
[邪恶力量 第12季第9集]
(上报  连接已建立  继续)
我是米克·戴维斯
This is Mick Davies,
提交状态更新报告B3
filing Status Update Bravo Three.
按照指示  我一直在尝试打入
As instructed, I've been attempting to make inroads
美国猎人界
with the American hunters.
但遗憾的是  遭遇了一些挫败
But unfortunately, there's been a few setbacks.
我来给你描绘一下
Let me paint you a picture
一个没有怪物  没有恶魔
of a world without monsters or demons
没有任何晚上出没的讨厌鬼的世界
or any of those little buggers that go bump in the night.
一个再没有人会因为超自然生灵而死的世界
Of a world where no one has to die because of the supernatural.
一个新世界  一个更好的世界
Of a new world, a better world.
如果你跟我们合作  你将得到支持
Now if you work with us, you'll have support,
各种各样的支持
in every sense of the word.
需要传说
You need lore?
我们的图书馆是最大最好的
Our libraries are the biggest and the best.
你要钱  我们有钱
You want money? We have money.
你需要武器
You need weapons?
我们的装备你无法想象
We have gear you can't even imagine.
我的意思是  沃利
Now what I'm saying, Wally,
你需要我们这样的人  而我们需要你这样的猎人
is that you need people like us, and we need hunters like you.
我们只求  等我们找到你
Now all we ask in return is that when we call,
你就听命去该去的地方  做该做的事
you go where you're told and you do what you're told.
这是为了大局
For the greater good.
我看看你的手
Let me see your hands.
来  给我看看你的手
Come on, let me see your hands.
好吧
Yeah, all right.
挺软
Soft.
谢谢
Thank you.
你猎过魔吗
You ever hunt anything?
我是战术型的  长期策略
I'm more tactical. Long-term strategy.
好吧
Right.
听着  迈克
Listen, uh, Mike --
-米克  -无所谓
- Mick. - Whatever.
我不认识你
I don't know you,
我也不想听令于任何人
and I ain't looking to take any orders from anyone.
尤其是
Especially some...
英国小文员
...limey paper pusher.
-我想你并不理解  伙计  -我理解
- I'm not quite sure you understand, mate. - No, I think I do.
别介意
So no offense,
但拿着你的提议
but you can take your offer...
然后...
and you can...
塞进你菊花里吧
...shove it up your ass.
应该不会太疼
I'm sure it won't be too painful,
你手不是挺软嘛
what with those soft hands of yours, right?
这是汉堡的钱
That's, uh, that's for the burger.
简而言之  美国猎人
In short, the American hunters have proven...
很难搞
difficult.
至于温家兄弟
As for the Winchesters...
你抛下了他们
You left them.
不  我...
No, I...
迪恩叫我走的  那女人
Dean told me to go. The woman --
你还弄丢了
The one you lost?
我没有...我以为她...
I didn't. I... I thought that she --
别找借口了
Stop making excuses!
如果他们需要帮助  为什么不找我
Why...if they needed help, why didn't they call me?
你不在
You were out.
我们怎么会让这种事发生  卡西迪奥
How do we let this happen, Castiel?
吃饭了
Chow time!
帮不了你
Can't help you.
得了  克劳力  警察抓走了他们
Come on, Crowley. The police took them.
你在政府里有人
You have people in the government.
-你有间谍  -是吗
- You have spies. - I do?
但不管小鹿和松鼠现在怎么样
But whatever's happened to Moose and Squirrel,
显然  他们没有权限打探
apparently, it's above their pay grade.
你在乎他们被抓吗
Do you even care that they're gone?
不
No.
知道有多少厉害的东西
Do you know how many all-powerful beings
曾试图杀他们吗
have tried to kill them?
-大概知道  -我也是
- Roughly, yes. - As do I.
我也曾是其中之一
I was bloody one of them.
但萨姆和迪恩  他们就像疱疹
Sam and Dean? They're like herpes.
你还以为已经摆脱了他们
Just when you think they're gone...
哎呦  他们又回来了
Hello! The boys are back,
身后还留下一堆尸体
leaving a trail of bodies in their wake.
不管他们在哪
So wherever they are,
不管是谁抓了萨姆和迪恩
whoever has Sam and Dean,
这么说吧
Well...
套用劳伦斯·图拉德(摔跤手)的名句
in the immortal words of Lawrence Tureaud...
"我可怜那傻瓜"
"I pity the fool."
迪恩
Dean?
不
No.
他...
He's...
-玛丽  -嗯
- Mary? - Yeah.
我是艾莉西娅  阿沙的孩子
This is Alicia. Uh, Asa's kid.
听着  我和我哥哥
Look, I -- me and my brother,
我们在路易斯安那州办个案子
we're working this case in Louisiana.
我们以为是个南方狼人什么的
We thought it was some southern fried werewolf thing,
但是不止一个
but it's not one thing.
是一群
It's a pack.
这里有好多这怪物
There's, like, a billion of them down here,
我们需要帮助
and...we need help.
你在哪
Where are you?
谢谢你来见我
Thanks for meeting me.
我只想说  对不起
I just wanted to say... I'm sorry.
我当时很生气
I was angry, and...
萨姆和迪恩  那不怪你
Sam and Dean, that's not your fault.
不  你是对的
No, you were right.
我不该抛下他们的  我...
I should never have left them. I...
听到什么动静了吗
Have you heard anything?
我在执法机关的熟人不是退休  就是死了
All my law enforcement contacts are retired or...dead.
我在努力  但是
I'm trying, but...
你呢
You?
我一直安慰自己  他们没事
I keep telling myself they're fine.
-他们才不见了  -六周两天10小时
- They've only been gone - 6 weeks, 2 days, and 10 hours.
我们会找到他们的  卡西迪奥
We'll find them, Castiel.
我们会的
We will.
在那之前  我们...
Until then, we just...
我们在尽力了
We're doin' our best.
是吗
Are we?
听说密苏里州兰开斯特的杀人案了吗
Did you hear about the murders in Lancaster, Missouri?
没有
No.
好几个女人被撕烂喉咙
The women with their throats ripped out,
血被吸干
the blood drained?
吸血鬼
Vampires.
我在新闻上看到  就想
I saw it on the news and I thought,
萨姆和迪恩就会去调查这样的事
that's the sort of thing Sam and Dean would investigate.
他们会赶过去
They would roll into town,
拯救大局  杀掉怪物
save the day, kill the monsters.
但是他们走后
But with them gone...
我努力去查案  我努力了
I tried to work the case. I tried.
但我不知道我哪里做错了
But...I don't know what I did wrong.
我问问题
I...I asked questions,
但或许问的人不对
but maybe they were the wrong people
或是问的不对
or the wrong questions,
我就是找不到它
and I just -- I never found it.
没找到那怪物  根本没沾边
Never found the monster. Never even got close.
我走前又有三个女人被杀
And three more women died before I left town.
我逃跑了
Before I ran away.
那我们回去
So we go back.
你和我
You and me.
不
No.
不  我只会碍事
No, I'd only get in your way.
吃饭了
Chow time!
Yo, eat up.
该死
Crap.
怎么回事
What happened?
我在巡视  我做了心肺复苏
I was doing my rounds and I did CPR,
但他已经死了
but he was gone.
开另一间牢房  快
Get that other cell open. Now!
他死了
He's dead.
我不懂
I don't get it.
他们死在同一天
They both died on the same day?
这不...
That's not...
这怎么可能
How's that even possible?
你来说啊
You tell us.
好计划
Great plan.
这俩月来  我们什么都没做
For the last two months, we've done nothing
就干坐着玩蛋
but sit around with our junk in our hands
就因为你想干耗着
because you wanted to wait them out.
真是成功
That really worked.
-干得好  -那我...
- Yeah, nice job. - Well, I'm just gonna...
嗯
Yeah.
你不是希望他们死吗  他们死了
You wanted them dead. They're dead.
我希望他们得到惩罚
I wanted them punished.
我想看着迪恩·温彻斯特的眼睛
I wanted to look Dean Winchester in the eye and...
让他感觉到痛苦
...wanted him to feel it.
那...
Well, that...
真是完全不算心理有问题呢
that is totally mentally normal.
去死吧
Go to hell.
(语音信箱)
卡西迪奥  是我
Castiel, it's me.
我就是打来...
I'm just calling to...
你不用担心密苏里州那个怪物了
You don't have to worry about that thing in Missouri.
我在处理了
I'm handling it.
你没事吧
You good?
嗯  不算很好
Yeah, I've been better.
-但我经历过更糟的  -看来成功了
- I've been worse. - Looks like it worked.
到目前为止是
So far.
怎么...
H-how...
-我们在哪  -我不知道
- Where are we? - I-I don't know.
回答他
Answer him.
真的  他们每天蒙着我的眼睛
Seriously, they blindfold me every day
带我来上班的
before they bring me to work.
我...
I...
这地方  严格说是不存在的
This place, it's not supposed to exist.
(禁区  闲人止步)
安全
Clear.
这里是我的语音信箱
This is my voicemail.
开这个
Hey, should we take it?
留下你声音的邮件
Make your voice a mail.
别  大概是有追踪器的
No, it's probably got lowjack.
这里是我的语音信箱
This is my voicemail.
-拜托  小卡  -找到地图了
- Come on, Cass. - Got a map.
-干什么  -小卡
- What? - Cass.
迪恩
Dean?
哥们  好久不见
Hey, buddy. Long time.
怎么...
What...
怎么回事  你在哪
What happened? Where -- where are you?
你不会相信的  而且我也不知道
You wouldn't believe me, and I have no clue.
有发现
Got something.
好吧  看来那是麋鹿山
All right, looks like that's Elk Mountain,
那么那就是朗斯峰
which makes that Longs Peak.
好吧  看来我们在科罗拉多州
Okay, looks like we're in Colorado.
在落基山国家公园
In Rocky Mountain National Park.
往北走  应该能走到34号国道
if we head north, we should hit State Route 34.
-最终会到的  -听到了吗
- Eventually. - Did you get that?
-嗯  -那好  那里碰头
- Yes. - All right, meet us there.
等等  那里
Wait. Where?
沿路开  你会看到我们的  小卡
Just drive along the road, and you'll see us. And, Cass...
越快越好  我们时间不多
the sooner the better. We're kinda on the clock here.
等等  那是什么...
Wait, what does that...
-你没告诉他  -没
- You didn't tell him? - No.
-他们能追踪手机  -对哦
- They'll track the phone. - Right.
卡西迪奥
Castiel?
慢点说  什么
Slow...slow down. What?
天呐
Oh, God.
搞什么
The hell?
-下车  -这不是...
- There you go. - This isn't...
我把过他的脉  他们死了
I took his pulse. They were dead.
我也不清楚是怎么回事
Look, I got no idea what went down here.
或许他们买通了哪个守卫
Maybe they got to one of the guards.
或许这是什么放慢心跳的功夫
Maybe this is some slow your heartbeat kung fu crap.
我只知道  温家兄弟现在在逃
What I do know -- the Winchesters are out there.
这次  我们按我的办法来
And this time, we're doing it my way.
好了
All right!
两名逃犯  已逃跑约45分钟
We got two runners with about a 45-minute head start.
他们是杀人犯
These are killers.
看到他们  立刻击毙
So you get eyes, you pull the trigger.
出发
Let's move out.
你赶到得好快
You got here quickly.
嗯
Yep.
你觉得会是什么样的情况
What do you think we're walking into?
我不知道
I don't know.
我们可能需要后援
We may want backup.
克劳力和罗威娜
Crowley and Rowena?
地狱之王和他的女巫妈妈
The King of Hell and his mother, the witch?
希望我们能找到更好的
Hope we can do better than that.
-我可能有办法了  -好
- I may have an idea. - Good.
系好安全带
Seat belt on.
我开车很快
I drive fast.
很久没出外勤了吧
Long time since you've been in the field, huh?
如果你想回去...
I mean, if you need to head back...
我没事
I'm fine.
好吧  还有...一小时天黑吗
All right, so we got what? An hour till dark?
那么还有六小时到午夜
Which puts us at six hours till midnight?
差不多
That sounds about right.
迪恩  我们得谈谈这个
Dean, we gotta talk about this.
好吧  我们会谈的  好吗
Okay, we will. All right?
回头的
Later.
这就是你的主意
This is your idea?
他们差点杀了我儿子
The people that almost killed my boys,
就找他们做后援
they're gonna be our backup?
那个恶魔和他妈妈突然看上去不那么糟了
Suddenly, the demon and his mommy don't look so bad.
他们在路西法的事上帮过我们
They helped us with Lucifer.
路西法  魔鬼路西法吗
Lucifer? The Lucifer?
-是的  -等等
- Yes. - Wait, so
你是说  印第安那波利斯的事是
you're telling me what happened in Indianapolis was
你们去单挑魔鬼本人了
you took on the bleedin' Devil himself?
对
Yes.
你们赢了吗
Did you win?
是的
Yes.
厉害
Bravo.
但是萨姆和迪恩被抓了
But Sam and Dean were taken.
我们认为我们能救他们回来  但我们需要
We think we can get them back, but we need...
帮助
help.
那我们就帮忙
So we'll help.
是吗  这么简单
Really? Just like that?
温彻斯特太太  玛丽
Mrs. Winchester -- Mary...
我来这国家就一个目的  交朋友
I came to this country to do one thing -- make friends.
但你们这些美国猎人
But you American hunters, you're --
跟我们不是一路人
you're a different breed than our sort.
你们乖戾  多疑
You're surly, suspicious.
-你们不喜欢跟人合作  -这描述很准确
- You don't play well with others. - Well, that is accurate.
你们不信任不熟悉的人
You don't trust people you don't know,
哪怕他们带着礼物而来
even when they come bearing gifts.
这我没办法  但我能帮你
Now I can't help that, but I can help you.
如果消息传开  说我们帮忙
And if word were to get out that we did our part
救了萨姆和迪恩·温彻斯特  那么
to save Sam and Dean Winchester, well,
也对我们有好处  是吧
that's just good business, innit?
谁知道呢
And who knows.
等这一切结束  我们或许还能成为朋友
When all this is over, we might even be friends.
我们认为萨姆和迪恩被关押在
We think Sam and Dean were being held somewhere
落基山国家公园的什么地方
in the Rocky Mountain National Forest.
94号地点
Site 94?
是一处私下的政府设施
It's a government facility, off-books.
影子行动
Shadow ops.
那种官方上讲不存在的地方
One of those places that officially doesn't exist.
那你们怎么知道的
Then how do you know about it?
我们收集情报  这是我们的工作
We gather information. It's our job.
他们叫我们去34号国道跟他们碰面
They told us to meet them off State Route 34.
那可是挺长一段路  具体在哪
Well, that's a long stretch of road. Where, exactly?
我不确定
I'm not sure.
我会叫我们技术员调出那一带的卫星图像
I'll our techs to put a satellite over the area.
你还有这本事
You can do that?
还不止
And so much more.
你知道我们会遭遇怎样的麻烦吗
Do you have any idea what sort of trouble we're walking into?
不知道
No.
很好
Oh, good.
我就喜欢惊喜
I do like a surprise.
-他们追上来了  -嗯
- They're on us. - Yeah.
该死
Damn it.
诺顿  回话
Norton, come in.
这里是诺顿  我在...
This is Norton. I'm on the ri--
诺顿  诺顿
Norton? Norton?
我是桑切斯  收到吗
This is Sanchez. Do you copy?
诺顿睡着了
Norton has gone night-night.
温彻斯特
Winchester.
-你是负责人吗  -对
- This the man in charge? - That's right.
我告诉你接下来会怎么样
Well, let me tell you how this is gonna go.
你要召集你的人
You're gonna call your boys
调头回去  没有人会受伤
and you're gonna turn around, and nobody's gonna get hurt.
不  接下来会这样
No, no. Here's how this is gonna go.
我带着我训练有素的士兵
I take my highly trained soldiers,
找到你们  你们会受伤
track your ass down, and you get hurt.
伤得很重
A lot.
你们没法一直跑下去
You can't run forever.
你们困在这里了
You're trapped out here.
看来我们沟通不畅
Well, what we have here is a failure to communicate.
不是我们跟你们困在了这里
'Cause we're not trapped out here with you.
是你们跟我们困在了这里
You're trapped out here with us.
这个就行
That'll work.
(急救箱)
上
Go!
你不会有事的
You'll live.
我说过  是你们被困住了
I told you. You're trapped.
凯普  开枪
Camp. Shoot him!
别
Don't.
枪给我
Hand me the gun.
想听真话吗
You want the truth?
总统被魔鬼附身了
The President was possessed by the Devil.
我们救了他
We saved his life.
这就是真相
That's the truth.
你知道了  你想怎么办都行
Now you can take that and do what you want with it.
但你敢来追我们
But if you come after us,
你知道会怎么样
you know what'll happen.
你们是谁
Who are you?
我们是拯救世界的人
We're the guys that save that world.
萨姆  迪恩
Sam! Dean!
-小卡  -小卡
- Cass. - Cass.
妈妈
Mom.
伙计
Hey, buddy.
妈妈  你们怎么找到我们的
Mom, how did y'all even find us?
他们帮了忙
They helped.
你们好
Hello, lads.
他们有热成像卫星  看到了你们
They have a thermal imaging satellite that saw you.
从太空看到的
From space.
我们没有卫星
We don't have one.
只是借了一个用了一下
Just borrowed it for a bit.
有说得上话的朋友
Friends in all the right places.
那么我们现在应该说谢谢了
Well, I guess this is where we're supposed to say thank you.
不必  很高兴能帮忙
No need. Happy to be of service.
再次帮忙
Again.
那好吧
Okay, then.
我们该走了
We should get.
我们丢下的人  他们随时会呼叫支援
The people we left, they'll call for backup any second.
你们留活口了
You left survivors?
他们是士兵  只是在尽职
They were soldiers, just doing what they were told.
但还是有点...不专业
Still...A bit unprofessional.
我们能应付
We'll handle it.
走吧
Let's get.
等等  你在猎魔
So wait, you're hunting?
就一点点
A little bit.
我就知道你放不下
Yeah, I knew you couldn't stay away.
时候到了
It's time.
怎么回事
What's happening?
是啊  迪恩
Yeah, Dean.
好啊
'Sup?
比莉
Billie?
那个死神
The reaper?
我不懂
I don't understand.
妈妈  那地方
Mom...that place...
只有一个办法能逃出来
There's only one way we were getting out of there,
活着是做不到的
and that wasn't breathing.
所以我叫了她
So I made a call.
比莉
Billie.
迪恩跟她谈了  然后比莉来见了我
Dean talked with her, and then Billie came to see me.
我们做了个交易
And we made a deal.
我们可以再死而复生一次
We'd get to die and come back one more time,
但作为交换
but in exchange...
午夜  要有一个温彻斯特道别
Come midnight, a Winchester goes bye-bye.
道永别
Like, permanently.
这
And that
我可期待很久了
is something I've been looking forward to for a long time.
-你为什么  -我们已经死了
- Why would you - We were already dead.
关在那牢房里  什么都没有
Being locked in that cell with nothing...
我去过地狱
I've been to Hell.
这比那还糟
This was worse.
至少这样  我们中还有一个能继续下去
At least this way, one of us gets to keep fighting.
你们不非得这么做的
You don't have to do this.
就是非得
Yeah, they do.
我们约定好的
We made a pact.
血盟
Bound in blood.
打破誓言
You break that,
会有很严重的后果
there's consequences on a cosmic scale.
谁来呢
So who's it gonna be?
我
Me.
-妈妈  不  -妈妈  不
- Mom. No. - Mom. No. No.
你说午夜时  要死一个温彻斯特
You said come midnight, a Winchester dies?
我也是温彻斯特
I'm a Winchester.
我可以接受
Works for me.
-妈妈  -不要
- Mom! - Don't!
我爱你们
I love you.
小卡  你做了什么
Cass, what have you done?
必须做的
What had to be done.
这个世界
You know this world,
这个可悲  在劫难逃的小世界
this sad, doomed little world,
它需要你们
it needs you.
它需要每一个温家人
It needs every last Winchester it can get,
我不会让你们死的
and I will not let you die.
我不会让你们任何人死
I won't let any of you die.
我不会让你们牺牲自己
And I won't let you sacrifice yourselves.
你们对我太重要了
You mean too much to me,
你们太重要了
to everything.
是啊  你们做了个交易
Yeah, you made a deal.
一个愚蠢的交易  而我违约了
You made a stupid deal, and I broke it.
不客气
You're welcome.
就这样  温家兄弟又回来了
And just like that, the Winchesters are back,
不管怎样
for better or worse.
没错  他们没有把一切都收拾干净  但是
True, they did leave loose ends, but...
那就是凯奇先生的工作嘛
that's what Mr. Ketch is for.
所有知道
Every person who knew about
萨姆和迪恩的刺杀小历险的人
Sam and Dean's little adventure in assassination
都已经处理好了
has been dealt with.
就这世界看来
As far as the world's concerned,
这事根本没发生过
it never even happened.
我们可不需要美国政府
The last thing we need is for the United States government
到处打探  问问题
sniffing about, asking questions.
至于打入美国猎人界的事
And as for making inroads with the American hunters,well,
有好消息
good news.
我来给你描绘一下
Let me paint you a picture
一个没有怪物  没有恶魔
of a world without monsters or demons
没有任何晚上出没的讨厌鬼的世界
or any of those little buggers that go bump in the night.
一个再没有人会因为超自然生灵而死的世界
Of a world where no one has to die because of the supernatural.
一个新世界  一个更好的世界
Of a new world, a better world.
继续说
I'm listening.